Guide to the University Marshal records, 1825-2005 RG0043
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
University Marshal records
1825-2005
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
RG0043
27.5 Linear Feet
Collection include commencement programs, budgets, scripts, and videotapes.
Restrictions on Access
Some records may be restricted.
Acquisition Information
Materials acquired through transfers from campus offices.
Historical or Biographical Note
The University Marshal reports to the Executive Vice President for Academic Affairs, and oversees official functions at the University, such as commencements, the conferring of honorary degrees, opening convocation for the school year, and other special ceremonies. Robert Jones, professor of Religion, held the post for twenty years, from 1969-89, during which time the ceremonial mace came into use (1981). Before him, John Latimer, professor of Classics, served in the position from 1953-69. N.B. This history note was written in 2005
Scope and Contents
Materials in this collection include commencement programs, budgets, scripts, and videotapes. They range in date from 1825 to 2005 and were transferred to the University Archives by the University Marshal. Note that not all series have been processed. Please ask staff for assistance.
Collection Organization
Organized in four series: Convocation records; Programs and addresses; Office files; and Commencements and convocations.
General
Speeches; Washington (D.C.); Budget; Events; Commencement ceremonies -- Washington (D.C.); George Washington University--History; Johnson, Lady Bird; George Washington University; Latimer, John Francis
- Convocation records, 1971-1989; RG0043 Series 1; 12 Linear feet (Box 5, Box 9)
  Scope and Contents note
  This series includes records from commencements and convocations. It includes programs, budgets, memorial services, videotapes, scripts, and speakers. They range in date from 1971-1989.
  - Winter convocation, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Graphics-winter convocation, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Script winter convocation, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Winter convocation, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Winter convocation, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Student medalist, MLK, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - MLK (Martin Luther King Convocation), 1989 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - MLK, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Spring commencement, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Script-spring commencement, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Spring commencement, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Medical School Commencement program spring, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - National Law Center Commencement program spring, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Commencement program spring, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Commencement program winter, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Commencement program spring, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Commencement program spring, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Commencement program winter, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Commencement program spring, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Commencement program winter, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Commencement program spring, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Commencement program winter, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Commencement program spring, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Commencement program winter, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Commencement program spring, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Commencement program winter, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Commencement program spring, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Commencement program winter, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Commencement program spring, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Commencement program spring, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - School of Government and Business Administration commencement script, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Commencement program winter, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Commencement program spring, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Commencement program winter, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Commencement program winter, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Commencement program spring, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Commencement program winter, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Commencement program spring, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Commencement program winter, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Annual report, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Inauguration, undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - MLK medal, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Honors convocation, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Opening convocation, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Opening convocation, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Public Cer., 1986 -1988 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Inauguration committee, undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Sping grad videos, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Inaugural scripts, undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Script-summer, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Spring commencement, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Script winter, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Winter convocation, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Commencement address, undated (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Sunday Star-120 yrs. of GWU, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Mace, undated (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Publ. ceremonies questionnaire, undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Homecoming, undated (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Banner project, undated (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Senior class, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Sesquicentennial year, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Lloyd Harman Elliott retirement, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - ASA Briggs convocation, undated (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Luther Rice bicentennial, undated (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Lecture sp. Convocation committee, undated (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Luther Rice bicentennial speakers, undated (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Special events speaker, undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Opening convocation, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Opening convocation, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Fall convocation, 1987 -1988 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Honors convocation, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Honors convocation, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Honors convocation, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Honors convocation, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Academic convocation, 1988 -1989 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Memorial, undated (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Memorial blanks, undated (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Oppenheim memorial service, undated (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Budget, 1987 -1988 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Budget, 1987 -1988 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Budget, 1987 -1988 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Honors and academic convocation, undated (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Honors academic convocation, 1986 -1987 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Scheduling, 1988 -1989 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Marshal, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - 188 tapes, undated (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Martin Luther King Jr. holiday committee, undated (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - MLK's birthday, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - MLK program, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - MLK, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - MLK, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Public ceremonies, 1982 -1983 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Public ceremonies, 1983 -1984 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Old publ. cer St. H, 1984 -1985 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Faculty dinners 25 years, undated (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Faculty dinner, 1983 -1987 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Faculty luncheon and emeriti and 25 yr. awards, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Faculty luncheon, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Emeriti and 25 year mailing, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Honors and academic convocation, 1985 -1986 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Asa Briggs convocation, undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Samples, undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Elliot G/A, undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Tapes, undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Honorary degrees, 1987 -1988 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - MLK, 1987 -1988 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - GW TV-Logistics, undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Scheduling-public ceremonies, 1987 -1988 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Faculty senate committee on H/A convocations, 1986 -1987 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Academic honors display, undated (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Cteon honors and academic convocation, 1987 -1988 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Commencement-seating, undated (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Opening convocation, 1987 -1988 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Winter convocation, 1987 -1988 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - University Marshal, 1968 -1969 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Dr. Jones-public ceremonies, undated (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Budget, 1988 -1989 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Inauguration budget, undated (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Suggestions for commencement ceremonies, undated (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Faculty lunch, 1988 -1989 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Personnel - Marshal's office, undated (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - University committee on public ceremonies, 1986 -1987 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Committee on university and urban affairs, 1977 -1978 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Script-spring, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Winter convocation, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Winter convocation, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Spring convocation, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Winter convocation-spring, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Fall convocation, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Commencement fact sheet and acc. letter, undated (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence re chaplains, undated (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Distinguished service award, undated (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Evaluation of commencements, undated (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Dean's letter-planning commencement, undated (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Honorary degree nomination forms, undated (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - GW awards and prizes, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - GW awards and prizes, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - GW awards-spring, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Honor societies-lists, 1978 -1984 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Honor societies, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Honor societies, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Honor societies, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Memo file, 10/31/1984 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Honor societies, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Honor society-form letters, September, March, undated (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Emeritus professors, 1976 -1981 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Emeritus citations, undated (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Emeritus professors, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Honorary degree citations, 1959-1990 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Honorary degree citations, undated (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Preparing honorary degree citations suggestions, undated (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Seating diagrams (Smith Center, Lisner Auditorium), undated (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Speakers and honorary degrees, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Speakers and honorary degrees, 05/1983 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Speakers and honorary degrees, 05/1982 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Speakers and honorary degrees spring, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Speakers and honorary degrees winter, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Commencement spring, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Script-spring, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Script-winter, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Script-winter, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Script-spring, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Script-winter, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Script-spring, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Student awards, prizes, undated (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Order of exercise, undated (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Suggestions for speakers, undated (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Script-spring, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Commencement tapes-spring, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - "The Elliot Years" The GW University, undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Elliott request, undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Opening convocation, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Spring commencement tapes, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Seating, undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Spring commencement, undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Faculty luncheon, undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Honors convocation, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Opening convocation, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Commencement prizes, awards, honors, undated (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Winter convocation script, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Board of trustees, undated (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Academic costume responses, undated (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Spring commencement, 1987 -1988 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Commencement publication, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Budget, 1985 -1986 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Budget, 1986 -1987 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Memorial programs, undated (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Farrington memorial service, undated (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Memorial service, Marvin D. Green, undated (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Elmer Louis Kayser service, undated (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Memorial service-Lawrence Leite, undated (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Memorial service-Bernard Levy, undated (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Memorial service-G. Lippitt, undated (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Memorial service-Guido Mazzeo, undated (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Memorial service-R.A. Moore, undated (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Singman memorial service, undated (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Edwin L. Stevens memorial service, undated (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Special convocation Elliade, undated (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Honors convocation, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Honors convocation, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Honors convocation, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Honorary degree nominations-winter convocation, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Honorary degree nominations-winter convocation, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Honorary degree nominations-spring convocation, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Honorary degree nominations-winter convocation, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Honorary degree nominations-spring, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Honorary degree nominations-winter, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Honorary degree nominations-spring, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Martin Luther King observance, 01/1986 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Martin Luther King, Jr., 1987 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - MLK Jr. medal, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Public ceremonies committee, 1984 -1985 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Faculty senate committee on honors and academic convocations, 1985 -1986 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - University committee on public ceremonies, 1985 -1986 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Special convocations and lectures, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Winter convocation, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Winter convocation, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Spring commencement, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Senior class committee, undated (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Faculty luncheon, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Faculty luncheon, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Faculty luncheon, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Homecoming, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Homecoming, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - University flags, undated (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Budget History, undated (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - VHS-SEHO spring commencement, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - VHS-National Law Center spring commencement, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - VHS-School of Public and International Affairs spring commencement, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Beta-School of Education and Human Development commencement, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - VHS-winter convocation, 02/1987 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - VHS-winter convocation, 02/1987 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - VHS-winter convocation, 02/14/1988 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - VHS-School of Engineering and Applied Science spring commencement, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - VHS-fall convocation, 09/11/1987 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - VHS-MLK day-King tribute tape, 01/19/1987 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Audio-MLK tribute, 01/18/1988 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    General note
    6 copies
  - Audio tape-MLK celebration, 01/19/1987 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    19 cm/sec, 38 cm/sec
  - VHS-The inauguration of John A. Curry, Northeastern University, 01/19/1987 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Commencement Ceremony Video, May 20, 2007, RG0043 Series 1; 1 media Betacam SP (Box 9, Videocassette 1)
  - Commencement Ceremony DVD, May 20, 2007, raw footage, RG0043 Series 1; 2 media Contained on 2 DVDs (Box 9, Dvd 1, Dvd 2)
  - Commencement Speakers DVD, May 20, 2007, RG0043 Series 1; 2 media 2 copies of DVD (Box 9, Dvd 3, Dvd 4)
  - Law School Celebration, Commencement DVD, May 20, 2007, raw footage, RG0043 Series 1; 2 media Contained on 2 DVDs (Box 9, Dvd 5, Dvd 6)
- Programs and addresses, 1826-2005; RG0043 Series 2; 7.5 Linear feet (Box 12, Box 14, Box 4, Box 1, Box 15, Box 3, Box 2, Box 11, Box 9, Box 10, Box 7, Box 8, Box 5, Box 6)
  This series contains commencent and convocation programs and addresses for Columbian College, Medical and Law Schools. They range in date from 1826 to present.
  Formerly Acc#261.
  - Commencement Program, 12/20/1826 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Commencement Program, 12/21/1831 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Commencement Program, 10/03/1838 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Commencement Program, 10/07/1840 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Commencement Program, 10/07/1846 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Commencement Program, 06/30/1858 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Commencement Program, E Street Baptist Church, 06/29/1859 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Commencement Program, First Baptist Church, 06/27/1860 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Commencement Program, First Baptist Church, 06/29/1870 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Commencement Program, Lincoln Hall, Young Men's Christian Association Building, 06/28/1871 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Commencement Program, Lincoln Hall, 06/12/1878 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Commencement Program, Lincoln Hall, 06/11/1879 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Commencement Program, Lincoln Hall, 06/08/1881 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Commencement Program, University Hall, 06/11/1894 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Commencement Program, University Hall, 06/10/1895 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Commencement Program, New National Theater, 05/28/1900 --05/30/1900 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    Spring
  - Commencement Program, New National Theater, 05/27/1901 --05/29/1901 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Commencement Program, New National Theater, 06/03/1902 --06/05/1902 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Commencement Program, New National Theater, 06/01/1903 --06/03/1903 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Commencement Program, New National Theater, 05/30/1904 --06/01/1904 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Commencement Program, Memorial Continental Hall, 05/29/1905 --06/01/1905 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Commencement Program, Belasco Theatre, 02/22/1906 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    Winter
  - Commencement Program, Memorial Continental Hall, 06/06/1906 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Commencement Program, Memorial Continental Hall, 10/17/1906 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    Fall
  - Commencement Program, Memorial Continental Hall, 06/05/1907 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Commencement Program, Belasco Theatre, 10/16/1907 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Commencement Program, Belasco Theatre, 06/03/1908 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Commencement Program, University Hall, 10/21/1908 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Commencement Program, Belasco Theatre, 02/22/1909 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Commencement Program, Belasco Theatre, 06/09/1909 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Commencement Program, Belasco Theatre, 02/22/1910 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Commencement Program, Belasco Theatre, 06/08/1910 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Commencement Program, New Masonic Hall, 02/22/1911 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Commencement Program, Belasco Theatre, 06/07/1911 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Commencement Program, Memorial Continental Hall, 06/05/1912 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Commencement Program, Memorial Continental Hall, 06/11/1913 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Commencement Program, Memorial Continental Hall, 06/10/1914 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Commencement Program, Assembly Hall, Dept. Arts & Sciences, 10/29/1914 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Commencement Program, Assembly Hall. Dept. Arts & Sciences, 02/22/1915 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Commencement Program, Memorial Continental Hall, 06/09/1915 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Commencement Program, Assembly Hall, Dept. Arts & Sciences, 02/22/1916 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Commencement Program, Memorial Continental Hall, 06/07/1916 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Commencement Program, Assembly Hall, Dept. Arts & Sciences, 02/22/1917 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Commencement Program, Central High School Auditorium, 06/06/1917 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Commencement Program, Assembly Hall, Dept. Arts & Sciences, 02/22/1918 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Commencement Program, Central High School Auditorium, 06/05/1918 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Commencement Program, New Masonic Temple Auditorium, 02/22/1919 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Commencement Program, Central High School Auditorium, 06/18/1919 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Commencement Program, Central High School Auditorium, 02/23/1920 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Commencement Program, Central High School Auditorium, 05/31/1920 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Commencement Program, Assembly Hall, Dept. Arts & Sciences, 10/28/1920 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Commencement Program, Central High School Auditorium, 02/22/1921 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Commencement Program, Central High School Auditorium, 06/08/1921 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Commencement Program, Concordia Church, Auditorium, 10/27/1921 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Commencement Program, Central High School Auditorium, 02/22/1922 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Commencement Program, Memorial Continental Hall, 06/07/1922 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Commencement Program, Concordia Church Auditorium, 10/26/1922 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Commencement Program, Memorial Continental Hall, 02/22/1923 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Commencement Program, Memorial Continental Hall, 06/06/1923 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Commencement Program, Concordia Church Auditorium, 10/25/1923 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Commencement Program, Memorial Continental Hall, 02/22/1924 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Commencement Program, Poli's Theatre, 06/04/1924 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Commencement Program, Corcoran Hall, 10/28/1924 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Commencement Program, Memorial Continental Hall, 02/23/1925 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Commencement Program, Washington Auditorium, 06/03/1925 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Commencement Program, Corcoran Hall, 10/20/1925 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Commencement Program, Memorial Continental Hall, 02/22/1926 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Commencement Program, Washington Auditorium, 06/09/1926 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Commencement Program, Memorial Continental Hall, 02/22/1927 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Commencement Program, Washington Auditorium, 06/08/1927 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Commencement Program, Memorial Continental Hall, 02/22/1928 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Commencement Program, Washington Auditorium, 06/13/1928 (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Commencement Program, Washington Auditorium, 02/22/1929 (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Commencement Program, Washington Auditorium, 06/12/1929 (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Commencement Program, Memorial Continental Hall, 10/09/1929 (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Commencement Program, Constitution Hall, 06/11/1930 (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Commencement Program, Memorial Continental Hall, 10/15/1930 (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Commencement Program, Constitution Hall, 02/23/1931 (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - Commencement Program, Constitution Hall, 06/10/1931 (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - Commencement Program, Corcoran Hall, 10/31/1931 (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - Commencement Program, Constitution Hall, 02/22/1932 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Commencement Program, Constitution Hall, 06/15/1932 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Commencement Program, Constitution Hall, 10/13/1932 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Commencement Program, Constitution Hall, 02/22/1933 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Commencement Program, Constitution Hall, 06/07/1933 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Commencement Program, Corcoran Hall, 10/18/1933 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Commencement Program, Constitution Hall, 02/22/1934 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Commencement Program, Constitution Hall, 06/06/1934 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Commencement Program, The Gymnasium, 10/17/1934 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Commencement Program, Constitution Hall, 06/05/1935 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Commencement Program, 10/16/1935 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Commencement Program, Constitution Hall, 02/22/1936 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Commencement Program, Constitution Hall, 06/10/1936 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Commencement Program, Constitution Hall, 02/22/1937 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Commencement Program, Constitution Hall, 06/09/1937 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Commencement Program, Constitution Hall, 02/22/1938 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Commencement Program, Constitution Hall, 06/08/1938 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Commencement Program, Constitution Hall, 02/22/1939 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Commencement Program, Constitution Hall, 06/14/1939 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Commencement Program, Constitution Hall, 02/22/1940 (Box 2, Folder 20)